目覚めては繰り返す
Day after day, I awake in a daze,
mezamete ha kurikaesu nemui asa ha
目覚めては繰り返す　眠い朝は
眠い朝は
襟のタイをきつく締め
And fasten my collar tightly.
eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
襟のタイをきつく締め
教室のドアくぐると
As I walk through the door to my classroom,
kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to hon no sukoshi
教室のドアくぐるとほんの少し
ほんの少し胸を張って歩き出せる
I have the slightest bit of pride.
mune wo hatte arukidaseru
胸を張って歩き出せる
Then a wind rushed through that normal, everyday life.
sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
そんな日常に吹き抜ける風
そんな日常に
吹き抜ける風
聞こえた気がした　感じた気がしたんだ
I have a feeling I can hear it,
kikoeta ki ga shita
聞こえた気がした
I have a feeling I can sense it,
kanjita ki ga shitanda
感じた気がしたんだ
震えだす 今この胸で
Beginning to tremble within my chest.
furuedasu ima kono mune de
震え出す今この胸で
I have a feeling it's on its way,
mou kuru ki ga shita
もう来る気がした
As the millions of stars began to disappear,
ikuoku no hoshi ga kiesatteku no wo
幾億の星が消え去ってくのを
I sent them on their way,
miokutta
見送った
見送った 手を振った
Waving my hand,
te wo futta
手を振った
良かったねと
Whispering, "Congratulations".
yokatta ne, to
よかったね、と
翻譯 夏 今矢瘋
Lecture Building
Headmaster's Room
特效 saber 時間&後期 月染不透
萌月諸神聯合譯製
Why is the new song a ballad?
なぜ　新曲がバラード
いけない
It shouldn't be?
陽動にはね
It's not fit for diversion.
Hey...
その
陽動ってのは何なんだ
What's this "diversion" about?
トルネードのとき聞いてなかったの
Were you not listening during Tornado?
She's a part of the school rock band that gains the students' approval.
彼女が校内でロックバンドを組んでいて
一般生徒の人気やを勝ち得ている
私たちはかれらに直接危害を加えないけど
We don't hurt them, but at times we make use of them, and should they get in our way,
ときには利用したり
we have to get them out of the area.
妨げになるときは その場から排除しなくてはならない
At times like that, she and her girls act as a diversion.
そういうとき　彼女たちが陽動するの
エヌピーシーのくせに　みいはあなやつらだなあ
What lowbrow NPCs.
More like her band has that much skill and charisma.
つまり　彼女たちのバンドには
それだけの実力と魅力があるってことだ
So?
で　だめなの
It's a no-go?
A ballad is a bit...
バラードはちょっとね
If they listen so quietly and attentively, we couldn't do anything wild.
しんみり聞き入っちゃったら
私たち派手に立ち振る舞えないじゃない
そう　じゃあ没ね
I see. Then I guess I'll need to trash it.
それじゃ気を取り直して
On a different note, the next announcement is for everyone.
総員に通達する
Otonashi-kun.
音無くん
カーテン閉めて
Close the curtain, will you?
The next operation will focus on retribution: Operation Tenshi Domain Infiltration.
今回のオペレーションは天使エリア侵入作戦のリベンジを行う
We'll be rolling out in 3 days.
決行は三日後
So we're going with that strategy?
その作戦ですか
Oh yeah.
ですが　前回は
However, last time-
This time, he will be coming with us.
今回は　彼が作戦に同行する
Greetings.
よろしく
He just popped out from behind the chair?!
椅子の後ろから
メガネ被り
He has glasses, too.
ゆりっぺ　なんの冗談じゃ
Yurippe, what kinda joke is this?
そんな青瓢箪が使い物になるのかよ
What good is that shrimp gonna do us?
Come now, don't be like that.
まあ　まあ
そう言わないでくれる
Fine! In that case!
はあ　なら   試してやろ
I'll test him!
I bet you don't have any friends, huh?
お前　友達いないだろ
3.1415926535...
3.14159 26535 89793 23846 26433…
…83279 50288 41971 69399 37510…
Stop! Stop it!!
やめろ　やめてくれ
まさか　円周率だと
What?! Pi?!
…58209 74944 59230 78164 06286…
メガネ被り
He has glasses, too.
Please stop! He's a moron!
やめてあげて
その人アホなんだ
そ　私たちの弱点はアホなこと
Exactly. Our weakness is that we're all morons.
…20899 86280 34825 34211 70679…
リーダーが言うなよ
That's not something a leader should say.
During the last operation, we brought
our lack of intelligence to the forefront.
前回の侵入作戦では
我々の頭脳の至らなさを露呈してまった
…82148 08651 32823 06647 09384 46095……
しかし
However!
This time, we have him, the prodigy hacker.
今回は天才ハッカーの名を縦にした彼
ハンドルネーム竹山くんを
He will be added to our team, alias Takeyama-kun.
作戦チームに登用
エリアの調査を綿密に行う
We will have him perform thorough research regarding the domain.
今のは本名なのでは
You mean that wasn't his real name?
Call me...
僕のことは
...Christ.
クライストとお呼びください
見ろ
See there? You ruined his cool alias.
格好いいハンドルが台無しだ
さすが　ゆりっぺだぜ
Way to go, Yurippe.
So, what's this "Tenshi Domain"?
で　天使エリアってのは
It's where Tenshi lives.
天使の住処だ
"Where Tenshi lives"?
天使の住処？
W-What could it be like?
ど　どんなところで住んでいるんだろ
Wait. A hacker is necessary for a place like that?
待って
そんなところにハッカーが必要なのか
A computer is what controls the core of her hideout.
中枢はコンピューターで制御されてんだよ
機械仕掛か
So it's all mechanical?
そのどこかに神に通じる手段があるの
There should be a lead to God in there somewhere.
This is an incredible operation!
こいつはとんでも無い作戦だ
Since it's our second attempt, Tenshi is likely to be on higher alert.
二度目ということもある
天使も前以上に警戒しているはずよ
ガルデモには以上
We'll need a big show out of GirlDeMo.
派手にやってもらわないとね
You got it.
了解
Get chance and luck!
get chance you look
Below Second Bridge
Okay. Looking good.
よし
いい調子だ
Hey, aren't I getting way too used to this?
なんか　溶け込みまっくてねーか　俺
Well, in actuality, they aren't as bad as I first thought they were.
でも　最初の印象ほど
悪い奴らじゃねーような  あいつら
Billboard
Classroom Building B
So this is part of the grand diversion.
これが例の派手な陽動ってやつか
Oh, sorry. Did I surprise you?
ああ　ごめん   驚かしたか
Oh, it's you.
あなたでしたか
俺のことを知ってるの
You know me?
Yeah!
はい   いつもでかいのをもって歩いてる先輩が
The upperclassman who always walks
around with a big axe said something like,
奴は最悪をもたらすから
"Watch out for him, he only brings bad luck."
注意しろとかなんとか言ってました
あの野郎か
That bastard.
Hey, is it really okay to take up the whole gym like that?
でも　これ体育館占拠って大丈夫なのか
It's not all right at all!
そうりゃやばいですよ　前代未聞ですよ
Completely unheard-of before.
It's not a live where we're acting as a guerilla force,
しかもゲリラライブじゃなく
but a regular announced live concert.
告知ライブですしね
先生たちも放っておかないし
The teachers won't overlook this,
どんな邪魔は入るか　分からないですよ
so who knows what kind of interference we'll get.
But for this mission, I've been told that we need to gather people up, even if it means going this far.
でも今回の作戦は
そうしてでも人を集める必要があると聞きました
Girls Dead Monster, eh?
ガールズ　デッド　モンスターね
ところで　ええと
By the way, you're...
ユイです
I'm Yui!
I'm only a flunky in the Diversion Division.
まだ陽動班のしたっぱですが   でも　それでも満足です
But I'm perfectly fine with that! I mean, I get to help GirlDeMo!
だって　ガルデモお手伝いですよ
You know! Girls Dead Monster, GirlDeMo for short, is really amazing!
知ってますか
凄いんですよ「ガールズ　デッド　モンスター」
略してはガルデモは
They can play that well with only girls.
女の子だけであの演奏力
And above all, the presence that Iwasawa-san, the vocalist and lead guitarist, holds...!
そして  なんといっても
ボーカルアンドギターの岩沢さんの存在だ
作詞作曲までしちゃうんです
She even writes the lyrics, and composes the music!
私の気に入りはCrow Song
My favourite is "Crow Song."
サリバン転調はですね　思いきりが良くていいんですよ
The tempo of the chorus section is totally awesome!
歌詞はですね　まさに岩沢さんのことを
The lyrics, too. They're talking about her life.
Another great high-tempo song is "Alchemy". "Alchemy" is-
後々　盛り上がるのはですね
「アルケミー　アルケミーは…」
まだ　終わってません
I'm not done talking yet!
アルケミーはです
"Alchemy" is-
こんなところで油売ってる暇があるのか
You really have time to waste?
Go get working for your favourite GirlDeMo, why don't you?!
その大好きなガルデモのためにさっさと働けよ
Ah, that's right!
お　そうでした
'Scuse me, then!
ではこれで
Unused
Classroom
Classroom Building A
Whoops...
Sorry, I'll restring it right away.
悪い　すぐ張り直す
じゃ　休憩
Okay, we'll take five.
That was some heat in there.
すげぇ熱だった
I can understand why the NPCs get all excited over you guys.
確かに一般生徒が熱狂的なるのもうなずけよ
思わず聞き入った
I found myself tuning in.
Thank you.
ありがと
I heard you don't have any memories, right?
あんた　記憶がないんだってね
Yeah.
まあな
それ幸せだ
That's happiness.
Are your memories... well...
あんたの記憶も　その
Have you heard anyone else's yet?
誰かの記憶聞いた
Yeah, Yuri's.
ああ　ゆりの
ゆりのか
Oh, Yuri's?
あれは最悪ね
Hers are the worst.
Mine aren't as bad as hers.
私のはそこまでひどくない
"As bad"?
そこまで
It's really nothing special.
大した話じゃないってば
I couldn't sing the song I like...
好きな歌が歌えなかった   それだけ
That's all.
My parents were always fighting.
両親はいつも喧嘩ばかりしていた
I didn't even have my own room.
自分の部屋もなく
I would shrink myself into a small ball
in the corner of the room, and cover my ears.
その怒鳴り声の中
隅で小さく丸まって
耳を塞いだ
All I could do was to close myself into a protective shell.
自分の殻に閉じ籠もるしかなかった
There wasn't anywhere I could relax.
どこにも休まる場所はなかった
That's when I came across the band called Sad Machine.
そんな時出会ったのが  サッド　マシンというバンド
The vocalist was also from an unfortunate family.
そのボーカルも
私と同じ恵まれない家庭環境にいて
During the hard times, he would plug his ears with headphones, and escape into the world of music.
精神的に辛い時期は
耳をイヤホンで蓋して　音楽の世界に逃げ込んだと聞いた
私もそうしてみた
I started doing the same.
I felt like everything was being blasted away.
すべてが吹き飛んでいくようだった
Like the vocalist was screaming for me.
ボーカルが私の代わりに叫んでくれる
That he was singing for me.
歌えてくれる
常識ぶってるやつこそが間違っていて
I began to believe that those who spoke rationally were wrong,
泣いてるやつこそが正しいだと
and those crying out were right.
孤独なアタシたちこそが
It made me realise that we lonely people
were the ones who were truly human.
人間らしいんだと
理不尽を叫んで
That music screamed, tore apart, and destroyed the unfairness that existed.
叩きつけて
破壊してくれた
私を救い出してくれた
It... saved me.
こいつと出会ったのは雨のゴミ捨て場
I met this thing on a rainy day, by a trash bin.
So I started singing.
私は歌い始めた
I thought I had nothing left in life, but I had found song.
何もないと思っていた私の人生にも　歌があったんだ
Are you serious?
本気かい？
You could go anywhere with your grades.
君の成績なら　どこにだって
Well...
もう
両親には頼りたくないので
...I don't want to rely on my parents any more.
バイトしてお金を貯め
I worked part-time to make money, and went from one audition to another.
レコード会社のオーディションを受け続ける日々
I was determined that, after graduating, I would leave the house, go to Tokyo,
卒業と同時に私は絶対あの家を出て
上京して
and make a living out of music.
そして音楽で　生きていくんだ
そう思った
I was determined to...
あれ　疲れてるのかな
What?
Am I tired?
こんなんじゃギター弾けない
I can't play guitar like this...
I should skip playing on the street tonight and get some rest...
今夜の路上は中止して
休もう　か
When I awoke, I had lost my power over words.
次に目覚めたとき
私は言葉を話せなかった
I had anepia... due to a cerebral infarction as a result of head trauma.
頭部打撲
脳梗塞による失語症
原因は
The cause... was a blow during one of my parents' fights.
両親の喧嘩のとばっちりだった
運命を呪った
I cursed my fate.
I had nowhere I could escape to.
どこにも逃げ出せなかった
そのまま
My life ended there.
私の人生は　ここで終わった
Iwasawa!
岩沢
あ　ひさ子
Ah, Hisako. Okay!
オーケー
We're all tired of waiting.
待ち草臥れてるよ
Hey, amnesia boy.
記憶無しよ　やるよ
Keep it.
Her eyes...
さっきも   あれは
Those eyes were cursing life.
人生の理不尽を呪った目だ
She had an awful life, too.
彼女にも陰惨な人生がある
だれもミジンコになることを恐れてるわけじゃない
It isn't that people are afraid of turning into water fleas.
People here are all trying to fight against God.
ここにいる連中は全員が
神に抗おうとしているんだ
They're all trying to fight...
理不尽な人生を受け入れることに
...against their unfair lives.
抗おうとしているんだ
これぐらい見逃せよ生徒会長
Why don't you let it slip by, President?!
He's right! GirlDeMo's live concerts are our only entertainment here!
そうよ
ガルデモのライブは私たちにとっての唯一の楽しみなのよ
Don't take that fun away from us!
それを奪うな
Yeah! Yeah!
そうだそうだ　なあ
Right?
あれ？
Huh?
うん？
Where did she go?
どこ行った
まるで悪役ね
So I'm the bad guy?
Gym
いい
Listen up. This time, we'll be going in with a minimal number of people.
今回は最小限の人数で作戦を行う
Operation starts at 1900 today.
作戦決行は本日　一九○○
オペレーションスタート！
Operation, start!
The crowd's small.
少ない
You get a box seat.
特等席だぜ
It's time!
時間だ
さあ
All right.
Let's rock the roof off!
派手にやろうぜ
Clear!
クリア
よし　まずは侵入成功ね
Good. We made it in fine.
We're in Tenshi's Domain.
天使エリアへ侵入
Close the door already!
ドア閉めなさいよ
Takeyama-kun, you take care of the computer.
竹山君はコンピュータの方よろしく
クライストとお呼びください
Call me Christ.
いや　これって
Hey, isn't this...
ただの女子の部屋荒らしじゃないかよ
This is just scavenging a girl's room! It's a crime!
犯罪じゃねぇか
What do you think you're doing?
貴様何をする
Girls' Dormitory
女子寮だぞ
This is the girls' dormitory! Turn the lights out!
電気を消せ
You said it was computer-controlled, didn't you?!
しかもコンピュータで制御だぁ？
パソコン一台あるだけじゃねぇかよ
It's just one PC!
パスワード
Password...
前は誰もわからなかったの
Nobody could guess it last time.
I see. So this is where I get to show my skills.
なるほど
僕の力の見せ所だ
Starting analysis.
解析に入ります
Oh? Guess he's somewhat useful, after all.
一応使えるみたいだな
こらこら
Hey, come on...
プライバシーの侵害だっつーの
You're violating someone's privacy!
うるさい奴だ
Shut your mouth.
それ以上騒ぐなら　喉元掻っ切るぞ
If you dare keep talking, I'll slice your throat open!
んだよ！
Screw you all! I was just starting to think better of you guys!
ちょっとお前らのこと見直したところなのによ
どうして
Why? There should be more coming...
もっと集ってくれ
アルケミー？
"Alchemy"?! So early in the concert...
こんな序盤で
Go!
いいぞ！
無限に生きたい
I want to live forever;
mugen ni ikitai
無限に生きたい
if I was able to live forever... all my dreams would come true.
mugen ni ikiraretara subete kanau
無限に生きられたら　全て叶う
無限に生きられたら
全て叶う
でもいろんなものが
But there are so many things chasing after me:
demo ironna mono ga atashi wo ouikondeku
でもいろんなものがあたしを追い込んでく
私を追い込んでく
It's "Alchemy"!
My time remaining, the coordinates of my dreams and their destination,
ikiru nokorijikan yume no zahyou yukue
生きる残り時間　夢の座標　行方
生きる残り時間
夢の座標を狂え
All very important things, but...
zenbu daiji na mono nanoni
全部大事なものなのに
Let's hang around here for a bit and eat all the sweet things we can,
iisa kokora de chotto amai mono tabete iko
いいさここらでちょっと甘いもの食べていこ
いざ　ここらでちょっと
甘いもの
食べていこう
そういう思考停止　あまり得意になった
I've become really good at doing nothing but distracting myself.
souiu shikouteishi bakari tokui ni natta
そういう思考停止ばかり得意になった
歩いてきた道振り返ってゆこう
If I look back on the road I've walked,
aruitekita michi furikaeru to
歩いてきた道振り返ると
こら お前たち　何してる　大人しく寮に戻れ
Hey, you guys!
What do you think you're doing?!
Return to the dorms at once!
やだよ　ぜってぇ見たいもん
I'm fed up with having had nothing but bad experiences,
iya na koto bakkari de mou unzari da yo
イヤなことばっかりでもううんざりだよ
Forget it! We wanna hear this!
嫌なことばかりでも　前を向けるよ
Yeah! You guys get out of here!
そうよ　お前らこそ帰れ
そうだそうだ
Yeah! Yeah!
A life where everything I touched began to shine...
fureru mono wo kagayakashiteyuku
触れるものを輝かしてゆく
She's here...
現れやがった
...that's the kind of road I wanted to live walking.
sonna michi wo ikitekitakatta yo
そんな道を生きてきたかったよ
Dear fans, rock out even harder!
みんな　もっと盛り上がってくれ
そんな道を作るから
No, it's not they themselves...
いや
そうされるのは誰でもない
笑ってよ
あたしたちのチカラなんだ！
It's our skill that incites them!
天使　出現しました
Tenshi has arrived.
Roger.
了解
竹山君
Takeyama-kun?
今　パスワードを高速で割り出すプログラムを走らせてます
I'm running the password cracking program right now.
It will be finished shortly.
すぐ終わります
Also, please call me Christ.
あと　僕のことはクライストとお呼びください
入りました
We're in.
Well done, Takeyama-kun!
よくやったわ竹山君
全てのデータ写して
Copy all the data!
That would take too much time.
時間が掛かりすぎます
It would take at least an hour to do that.
一時間は必要です
あと　僕のことはクライストとおっ…
Also, please call me Ch-
ハードディスクごと引っこ抜くか
Why not take the hard disk with us?
She'll know we were here.
ばれるじゃない
どうして
Then what should we do?
兎に角あやしいデータを見せて　竹山君
Just show us some critical-looking data, Takeyama-kun!
クライストです
It's Christ.
Student roster?
学生リスト？
エヌピーシーっ
NPCs... No, we're in the list, too.
いや　あたし達も混ざってるか
単なる名簿だろ
It's only a roster, isn't it?!
怪しいデータなんてどこにもねぇ
There's no suspicious data! This really is just a crime!
やっぱりただの犯罪行為じゃねぇかよ　だまれ！
Shut up!
陽動班　取り押えられました
The Diversion Division has been detained.
天使も戻ります
Tenshi will be returning.
チッ　ここまでね
I guess this is it.
今回も得るもの無しっか
Nothing gained this time, either.
退散するわよ
We'll retreat.
くそ　ふざけんなよ
Damn you! This is crap!
やめてあげて
Stop this!
They're doing this for us!
俺たちのためなんだよ
放してやってくれよ
Let go of them!
彼女たちの音楽が支えになってるの　お願い
Their music is our life! Please!
今までは大目に見てやってただけだ
We were only letting it slide until now!
Don't be so full of yourselves!
図に乗るな！
We're confiscating all the instruments.
楽器は全て没収だ
You won't be using these, not even in the school festival!
学園祭でも無し
二度とこんな真似はさせんぞ
これは捨てても構わないな
You don't mind if this is thrown away, do you?
Don't touch that...
触るな
Don't...
それに…それに…触るな！
Don't touch that!
Stop it!
止めんかッ
待って！
Wait!
Hand it over.
寄こせ
All the people who can't accept reality are off laughing,
joushiki butteru yatsu ga waratteru
常識ぶってる奴が笑ってる
次はどんな嘘を言う
What lies will they choose to tell next?
tsugi wa donna uso wo iu?
次はどんな嘘を言う
And will they be able to treasure,
sore de erareta mono
それで得られたもの
What things they manage to gain?
daiji ni kazatteokeru no?
大事に飾っておけるの
大事に飾っておけるの？
新曲が…
A new song?
でも明日へと
But we must forge on toward tomorrow,
demo asu he to susumanakya naranai
でも明日へと進まなきゃならない
進まなきゃならない
That's why I'll sing this song.
dakara kou utau yo
だからこう歌うよ
だから
こう歌うよ
竹山君
Takeyama-kun!
はい　クライストとお呼びください
I'm on it. And please just call me Christ!
The you that is crying, the you that is sorrowful,
naiteru kimi koso kodoku na kimi koso
泣いてる君こそ孤独な君こそ
泣いてる君こそ
孤独な君こそ正しいよ
Is correct. It's human.
tadashii yo ningenrashii yo
正しいよ人間らしいよ
人間らしいよ
落した涙が
These falling tears tell me,
otoshita namida ga kou iu yo
落とした涙がこう言うよ
こう言うよ
That everything really is this beautiful. That it's not all a lie.
konna ni mo utsukushii uso ja nai
こんなにも美しい嘘じゃない
こんなにも美しい
嘘じゃない
That we are our true selves...
hontou no bokura wo
本当の僕らを
本当の
僕らを
I'm so grateful...
arigatou
ありがとう
That's my life.
これがあたしの人生なんだ
To keep singing on like this.
こうして　歌え続けていくことが
それが生まれてきた意味なんだ
That's the meaning behind my life.
Just like how I was saved, I will save others the same way.
私が救われたように
こうして誰かを救っていくんだ
I finally... finally found it.
やっと
見つけた
岩沢？
Iwasawa?
Summarise the findings for us, Yurippe.
分った事をまとめてくれ　ゆりっぺ
Tenshi was creating her skills on her own.
天使は自分の能力を自分で開発してた
それは奇しくも　あたし達が武器を作る方法と同じだったのよ
And irritatingly enough, it was done exactly the same way as how we make weapons.
What do you mean by that?
それって　どういうこと
I don't have an exact answer yet. I can't say.
確信がないの
今はまだ言えない
何でだよ　水臭いぜ　ゆりっぺ
How come? Don't give us the cold shoulder like that, Yurippe.
あたし達と同じ方法を取る必要があると言うこと
It means there's a reason why she must use the same methods that we do.
そこから導き出されるのは　最悪の設定だ
The logical conclusion from that is we're in the worst possible set-up.
There is no God.
どこにも神など居やしない
Why doesn't she receive her skills from God if she's an angel?
どうして天使なら神からチカラを授からない
Why does she have to make them herself?
どうして自作などする必要がある
Then, there's one more issue here.
では　もう一つの案件です
岩沢さんは　どこに消えてしまったのか
Where has Iwasawa-san gone to?
Didn't Tenshi make her disappear?
天使に消されたんじゃないのか
ライブ中だぞ
In the middle of the concert?
じゃあ何が起きたって言うんだ
Then what do you say happened?
誰が一体岩沢さんを…
Who could have done this to Iwasawa-san...
誰も…
No one did.
She accepted it.
あの子が納得しちゃった
That's all there is to it.
それだけの話よ
消える条件は
The conditions for disappearance are obeying Tenshi and acting out a proper school life.
「天使の言い成りになって正しい学園生活を送る」
それだけじゃなかったんだ
I guess that isn't the only way it happens.
I've always walked this path alone; when I look back, everyone is so far away.
itsumo hitori de aruiteta furikaeru to minna ha tooku
いつもひとりで歩いてた　振り返るとみんなは遠く
いつも一人で歩いてた
振り返るとみんなは遠く
それでも私は歩いたそれが強さだった
Even so, I kept on walking. That was my strength.
soredemo atashi ha aruita sore ga tsuyosa datta
それでもあたしは歩いた　それが強さだった
もう何も 怖くない
"Nothing frightens me any longer", I mumble softly.
mou nanimo kowakunai sou tsubuyaitemiseru
もう何も恐くない　そう呟いてみせる
そうつぶやいてみせる
いつか　人は一人になって
．
Eventually, everyone ends up alone,
itsuka hito ha hitori ni natte
いつか人は一人になって
思い出の中に生きてくだけ
．
And is left with only their memories.
omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
思い出の中に生きてくだけ
孤独さえ愛し笑ってられるように
．
In order to appreciate even sorrow and continue smiling,
kodoku sae aishi waratterareru you ni
孤独さえ愛し笑ってられるように
私は戦うんだ
I'll keep on fighting,
atashi ha tatakaunda
あたしは戦うんだ
涙なんて見せないんだ
I won't show you my tears.
namida nante misenainda
涙なんて見せないんだ
Next Episode Preview
Play ball!
I'm sure to add strength to your team.
It's baseball.
Don't stop dancing!
I challenge you, kid.
She'll be filling in for Iwasawa?
I'll form the best team.
It really is a total mystery what you were doing until you died!
I'm Yui-nyan!
I'd say so, also.
Who are we fighting against...?
Your team has not enrolled in the event.
Will face a penalty game more painful than death.
Are you shivering?
That... would be the best feeling ever...